Guide to the Paul Davidoff papers, 1951-1985
Davidoff, Paul papers, 1951-1985
- Series III. Suburban Action Institute, alphabetical files
  - SAI - A Proposal- Suburban Action; An Institute for Suburban Research and Action; Davidoff and Gold, April 1969 (Box 10, Folder 32)
  - SAI - Advocate Planning For An Open Society (Box 10, Folder 33)
  - SAI - Suburban Action Employment- Practices (Box 10, Folder 34)
  - SAI - Conference, 1973 (Box 10, Folder 35)
  - SAI - Conference, 1974 (Box 10, Folder 36)
  - SAI - Periodic Report, 1976 (Box 10, Folder 37)
  - Saddle River, New Jersey (Box 10, Folder 38)
  - San Diego Advo. Paper (Box 10, Folder 39)
  - Sanibel (Box 10, Folder 40)
  - SASSO (Box 10, Folder 41)
  - Scarsdale, New York (Box 10, Folder 42)
  - SEED (Box 10, Folder 43)
  - Selma, Alabama (Box 10, Folder 44)
  - Serrano v. Priest (Box 10, Folder 45)
  - Special Lower Third Avenue Development District (Box 10, Folder 46)
  - Staten Island (Box 10, Folder 47)
  - Stauffer Chemical Company (Box 10, Folder 48)
  - "Suburban Opportunity Development. Project" - Proposal (Box 10, Folder 49)
  - Schultz; "Sub. Opp. Development Project" - Proposal (Box 10, Folder 50)
  - Suffolk County (Box 10, Folder 51)
  - Suffolk County Suit (Box 10, Folder 52)
  - Suffolk County (Box 10, Folder 53)
  - Suffolk Housing Services (Box 10, Folder 54)
  - Sutton, Percy (Box 10, Folder 55)
  - Swedish Planning Materials (Box 10, Folder 56)
  - Tarrytown Conference (Box 10, Folder 57)
  - Thomas, Gladys - Community Organizing (Box 10, Folder 58)
  - Testa, Frank (Box 10, Folder 59)
  - Thabit, Walter (Box 10, Folder 60)
  - Town Meetings (Box 10, Folder 61)
  - Toward Inclusive Land Use Controls - A Proposal (Box 10, Folder 62)
  - Transportation and Poverty (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Transportation (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Tri-State Regional Planning Commission (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Union Theological (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - United Nations (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - University of Pennsylvania (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Upper St. Clair Township (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Upper St. Clair (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - National Urban Coalition (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - Urban Development Corporation (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - Urban Land Institute (Box 11, Folder 11-12)
  - National Urban League (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - Urban League (Box 11, Folder 14)
  - National Urban Leadership Conference Columbus, September 9-10, 1974 (Box 11, Folder 15)
  - Valtierra (Box 11, Folder 16)
  - Valtierra v. Housing Authority (Box 11, Folder 17)
  - Valtierra Case - Briefs (Box 11, Folder 18)
  - Valtierra Case - Memo and Handwritten Notes (Box 11, Folder 19)
  - Valtierra Case - Record (Appendix) (Box 11, Folder 20)
  - Valtierra Case - Supreme Court Opinion (Box 11, Folder 21)
  - Valtierra Case - Newspaper Coverage (Box 11, Folder 22)
  - Valtierra Case - Lower Court Opinion (Box 11, Folder 23)
  - Valtierra Case - Analyses- NUC (Box 11, Folder 24)
  - Valtierra Case - Analyses- NCDH (Box 11, Folder 25)
  - Valtierra Case (Box 11, Folder 26)
  - Valtierra Case - Correspondence (Box 11, Folder 27)
  - Voluntary Society (Box 11, Folder 28)
  - Volunteers (Box 11, Folder 29)
  - C.D. Ward- Memo (Box 11, Folder 30)
  - Waterbury Zoning (Box 11, Folder 31)
  - WCBS Editorials (Box 11, Folder 32)
  - Welfare and Housing (Box 11, Folder 33)
  - Westbrook, Maine (Box 11, Folder 34)
  - Westchester County (Box 11, Folder 35)
  - Westchester Ethical Humanist Society (Box 11, Folder 36)
  - Westchester Case (Box 11, Folder 37)
  - Westchester CER (Box 11, Folder 38)
  - Westchester City Planning Department (Box 11, Folder 39)
  - Westchester Housing Commission (Box 11, Folder 40)
  - Westchester Residential Opportunities (Box 11, Folder 41)
  - Westchester Residential Opportunities (WRO) (Box 11, Folder 42)
- Series IV. Alphabetical files, 1970-1979
  - ADA Convention, 1970 (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - AIP (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - AIP Convention, 1971 (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - AIP Article - Suburban Action, September 1969 (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - AIP Detroit (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Berkshire Forum (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Cleveland Plan (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - Davidoff's Article (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Job Search, Fall 1974 (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - Davidioff's Speeches (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - Advocacy Speech, May 21, 1971 (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - Delray Beach, Florida (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - England/Friends (Box 12, Folder 13)
  - Forest Hills (Box 12, Folder 14)
  - Gaithersburg Study (Box 12, Folder 15)
  - Garden Cities Development Corporation (Box 12, Folder 16)
  - GLDC (Box 12, Folder 17)
  - GT & E - Stamford (Box 12, Folder 18)
  - Hatch, C. Richard (Box 12, Folder 19)
  - Bennett Harrison Review Urban Economic Development (Box 12, Folder 20)
  - Hoeh, David and Sandy (Box 12, Folder 21)
  - Housing Legislation (Box 12, Folder 22)
  - JAIP General (Box 12, Folder 23)
  - Land Use Chapter: State and Local Public Policy Reader, 1977 (Box 12, Folder 24)
  - Legislation: New York State (Box 12, Folder 25)
  - Leichter Bills (Box 12, Folder 26)
  - Letters (Box 12, Folder 27)
  - Margolis, Manny (Box 12, Folder 28)
  - McHUD (Box 12, Folder 29)
  - Metropolitan Areas (Box 12, Folder 30)
  - Metropolitan Council on Housing (Box 12, Folder 31)
  - "Middle America" (Box 12, Folder 32)
  - Negative Income Tax/Welfare Reform (Box 12, Folder 33)
  - New Democrat Article on Suburbs (Box 12, Folder 34)
  - New Forms of Suburban Zoning (Box 12, Folder 35)
  - New Jersey (Box 12, Folder 36)
  - New School, Spring 1972 (Box 12, Folder 37)
  - New School, Fall 1974 (Box 12, Folder 38)
  - New York Metropolitan Region Case Study, 1970 (Box 12, Folder 39)
  - New York City Master Plan Review (Box 12, Folder 40)
  - New York City Master Plan Speech - PD, April 1970 (Box 12, Folder 41)
  - New York Times Article (Box 12, Folder 42)
  - Ottinger (Box 12, Folder 43)
  - PARMA (Box 12, Folder 44)
  - George Raymond (Box 12, Folder 45)
  - R.C.A. (Box 12, Folder 46)
  - Regional F.H. Center- CER (Box 12, Folder 47)
  - Readington Township (Box 12, Folder 48)
  - Ribicoff, Abraham (Box 12, Folder 49)
  - Ribicoff - Act (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Richmond (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Robinson, Ira (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Schore, Albin (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - School Integration (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Squatters (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - Suburban Action (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - SAI - Current (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - SAI Poster, 1973 (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - Suburban Action - Statements (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - Suburban Action Conferences (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - Syracuse (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - Tobier Proposal (Box 13, Folder 13)
  - U.N. Housing (Box 13, Folder 14)
  - Urban Poverty v. Distributive Justice and Participant list of other conferences (Box 13, Folder 15)
  - Venezuela (Box 13, Folder 16-17)
  - Venezuela/Business (Box 13, Folder 18)
  - Venezuela (Box 13, Folder 19)
  - Westchester (Box 13, Folder 20)
  - Zoning Impact Study, 1964 (Box 13, Folder 21)
  - Zoning Study - National Commission On Urban Problems (Box 13, Folder 22)
  - Zoning - Douglas Commission Study (Box 13, Folder 23)
  - Zoning - Lower 3rd Ave. Development District (Box 13, Folder 24)
- Series V. Alphabetical files, 1980-1984
  - Accessory Apartments (Box 13, Folder 25)
  - Babylon (Box 13, Folder 26)
  - Brookhaven (Box 13, Folder 27)
  - Chinatown Case (Box 13, Folder 28)
  - Conversion Study Outline (Box 13, Folder 29)
  - Davidoff, Paul and Linda- Cita (Box 13, Folder 30)
  - Davidoff, Paul Letters, Clips, etc. (Box 13, Folder 31)
  - Davidoff - Work Honors, 1983 (Box 13, Folder 32)
  - P.D. - Odd Notes (Box 13, Folder 33)
  - Grosberg, Lawrence (Box 13, Folder 34)
  - Gross v. Moses - Full Employment (Box 13, Folder 35)
  - Housing Information Referral and Counseling Services, 1980 (Box 13, Folder 36)
  - Housing Trust Fund (Box 13, Folder 37)
  - Inclusionary Revitalization (Box 13, Folder 38)
  - Memorabilia, Paul (Box 13, Folder 39)
  - Mount Laurel (Box 13, Folder 40)
  - New Hampshire (Box 14, Folder 1-2)
  - NY FED (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Benefit, October 1983 (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Queens College (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Salary - Etc. (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Proposed workshops (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - Veatch Housing Evaluations (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - Yonkers (Box 14, Folder 9-11)
- Series VI. Metropolitan Action Institute, general files
  - MAI (Box 14, Folder 12)
  - MAI - Corporate Outreach Correspondence/Misc (Box 14, Folder 13)
  - MAI Funding (Box 14, Folder 14-15)
  - MAI Brochure (Drafts; data), April 1982 (Box 14, Folder 16)
  - MAI NYC Community and Advocacy Planning (Box 14, Folder 17-18)
  - MAI Reports (Box 14, Folder 19)
  - MAI - Accessory Apartments Advocacy Planning (Box 14, Folder 20)
  - MAI Lower East Side - Zoning (Box 14, Folder 21-22)
  - MAI misc. (Box 14, Folder 23)
  - MAI mailing lists (Box 14, Folder 24)
  - MAI correspondence (Box 14, Folder 25)
  - MAI C - misc. invoices (Box 14, Folder 26)
  - MAI Conferences and Seminars (Box 14, Folder 27)
  - MAI Office Annual Report- notes and drafts (Box 14, Folder 28)
  - MAI Inclusionary Zoning- proposals and drafts (Box 14, Folder 29)
  - MAI Annual Report - old drafts (Box 14, Folder 30)
  - MAI misc. correspondence, Summer-Winter 1982 (Box 14, Folder 31)
  - Mailing lists (Box 14, Folder 32)
- Series VII. Metropolitan Action Institute, alphabetical files
  - Annual report (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - APA Housing Fund (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - Annual report, 1982 (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - AHOPS- FY, 1978-1979 (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - Accessory apartments (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - Boyd, Lisa (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - CMA/Pratt (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - "C" misc (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence - incoming (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - Davidoff, Pual - resume (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - Division of State and Comm. Renewal (Box 15, Folder 11)
  - Davidoff (Box 15, Folder 12-13)
  - (MAI Goals) Distall, Dana (Box 15, Folder 14)
  - DuPont, Elise (Box 15, Folder 15)
  - Expert testimony 1-4 (Box 15, Folder 16)
  - Erasmus - work program (Box 15, Folder 17)
  - Ford Foundation (Box 15, Folder 18)
  - Fund raising file (Box 15, Folder 19)
  - Greenport (Box 15, Folder 20)
  - Hoboken Technical Assistant (Box 15, Folder 21)
  - HUD Report (Box 15, Folder 22)
  - HUD - audit (Box 15, Folder 23)
  - Inclusionary zoning (Box 15, Folder 24)
  - Goldman and Goldman (Box 15, Folder 25)
  - Interface (Box 15, Folder 26)
  - J.C. Penny Foundation (Box 15, Folder 27)
  - Luxury tax (Box 15, Folder 28)
  - Mailing list (Box 15, Folder 29-30)
  - Memos - incoming (Box 15, Folder 31)
  - Memorandum (Box 15, Folder 32)
  - MAI (Box 15, Folder 33)
  - MAI Board and Advisory Board (Box 15, Folder 34)
  - "M" misc (Box 15, Folder 35)
  - MAI's mailing list (master sheet) (Box 15, Folder 36)
  - MAI's Board members/meeting activity (Box 15, Folder 37)
  - "N" misc (Box 15, Folder 38)
  - NY FED (Box 15, Folder 39)
  - Originals - artwork (Box 15, Folder 40)
  - Proposals- inclusionary revitalization project (Box 15, Folder 41)
  - Publication announcement (Box 15, Folder 42)
  - Peekskill, Summer 1982 (Box 15, Folder 43)
  - City of Peekskill (Box 15, Folder 44)
  - Research foundation - financial statements (Box 15, Folder 45)
  - Resume (Box 15, Folder 46)
  - Symposium mailing list (Box 15, Folder 47)
  - Suburban action ins. (Box 15, Folder 48)
  - Starrett City (Box 15, Folder 49-50)
  - "S" misc (Box 15, Folder 51)
  - Single Family Conversions (Box 15, Folder 52)
  - SAI - Statements about policies, purposes, etc (Box 15, Folder 53)
  - Smith Haven Mall (Box 15, Folder 54)
  - MAI Board of Trustees (Box 15, Folder 55)
  - Urban Renewal Committee of S. Jamaica (Box 15, Folder 56)
  - Wyandanch Community Development Corporation (Box 15, Folder 57)
  - Warner Fund (Box 15, Folder 58)
  - Westchester Proposals (Box 15, Folder 59)
  - Yonkers - expert testimony (Box 15, Folder 60)
  - Peter Abeles Properties (Box 15, Folder 61)
  - A.N.H.D. (Box 15, Folder 62)
  - A.P.A. Minorities and Women (Box 15, Folder 63)
  - A.P.A. Conference (Box 15, Folder 64)
  - Asian-Americans v. Koch (Box 15, Folder 65)
  - Bedminster (Box 15, Folder 66)
  - Bronx Zoo (Box 15, Folder 67)
  - Board membership list and correspondence (Box 15, Folder 68)
  - Board's reply/support (Box 15, Folder 69)
  - Burke gross full employment (Box 15, Folder 70)
  - Casing Gambling (Box 15, Folder 71)
  - Chemical Bank Loan, 1981 (Box 15, Folder 72)
  - Barry Checkoway (Box 15, Folder 73)
  - Civil Liberties (Box 15, Folder 74)
  - CMA Non-State Contract- finances (Box 15, Folder 75)
  - CMA/Queens College Press Release CA, 1983 (Box 15, Folder 76)
  - Coalition mailing list (Box 15, Folder 77)
  - Cohen - dialogue (Box 15, Folder 78)
  - Comm. Consultant contract application (Box 15, Folder 79)
  - Connecticut Quintiles (Box 15, Folder 80)
  - Davidoff- advocacy and pluralism in planning (Box 15, Folder 81)
  - Davidoff- Cups/Mt. Laurel article/Planning, November 1983 (Box 15, Folder 82)
  - Davidoff- Starrett City (Box 15, Folder 83)
  - Davidoff- press clips/village voice (Box 15, Folder 84)
  - Joan Davidson (Box 15, Folder 85)
  - Displacement (Box 15, Folder 86)
  - Displacement, gentrification (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - Displacement, general (Phil) (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - Legal challenges to displacement (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - Measuring displacement (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - Montgomery Gateway Case (New Jersey) (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - Erasmus (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - Fair housing - New York State (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - The Fund for New Jersey (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - Foundation proposals (Box 16, Folder 9)
  - Gentrification (Box 16, Folder 10)
  - Getier, Keith (Box 16, Folder 11)
  - Grades (Box 16, Folder 12)
  - Greenport (Box 16, Folder 13)
  - Housing choices (Box 16, Folder 14)
  - Housing Trust Fund (Box 16, Folder 15)
  - HUD News Release (Box 16, Folder 16)
  - Infrastructure (Box 16, Folder 17)
  - Inclusionary Revitalization (Erasmus Neighborhood) (Box 16, Folder 18)
  - Inclusionary Zoning Conference, 1983 (Box 16, Folder 19)
  - The Guardian Life Insurance Policy (Box 16, Folder 20)
  - Independent Contractors (Box 16, Folder 21)
  - J-51 (Box 16, Folder 22)
  - Keith- Phil Protecting Existing Low Income Housing (Box 16, Folder 23)
  - U.S. Dept. of Labor (Box 16, Folder 24)
  - Lower East Side mailing list (Box 16, Folder 25)
  - MAI (Box 16, Folder 26-27)
  - MAI Tax forms (Box 16, Folder 28)
  - Mahwah (Box 16, Folder 29)
  - National Low Income Housing Coalition, January 1984 (Box 16, Folder 30)
  - MAI (Box 16, Folder 31)
  - MAI's Work Program (Box 16, Folder 32)
  - Merrian White (Box 16, Folder 33)
  - Metropolitan Mobility Data (Box 16, Folder 34)
  - Minimum floor area requirements (Box 16, Folder 35)
  - Mount Laurel/testimony (Box 16, Folder 36)
  - Dave Muchnick (Box 16, Folder 37)
  - Municipal Low Income Housing Coalition (Box 16, Folder 38)
  - National Low Income Housing Conference, 1984 (Box 16, Folder 39)
  - NYFED (Box 16, Folder 40)
  - New York State for Fair Housing Regulations (Box 16, Folder 41)
  - Nuclear Freeze Resolutions (Box 16, Folder 42)
  - New York Times (Box 16, Folder 43)
  - Panel of Americans (Box 16, Folder 44)
  - Peekskill (Box 16, Folder 45)
  - Penn Yards (Box 16, Folder 46)
  - Periodic report, November 1979 (Box 16, Folder 47)
  - Personal letters (Box 16, Folder 48)
  - Port Arthur New Town Case (Box 16, Folder 49-50)
  - Port Authority (Box 16, Folder 51)
  - Poverty course, Fall 1983 (Box 16, Folder 52)
  - Q-2000- Grad Course, Spring 1982 (Box 16, Folder 53)
  - Queens College Year 2000 Project (Box 16, Folder 54-55)
  - Resumes (Box 16, Folder 56-57)
  - Cindy Roeser's Veatch Program (Box 16, Folder 58)
  - Sheref (Yazicioglu) (Box 16, Folder 59)
  - Starret Article (Box 16, Folder 60)
  - Taconic- Mahwah (Box 16, Folder 61)
  - Term papers (Box 16, Folder 62)
  - Tax Exemption Forms (Box 16, Folder 63)
  - Tri-State Regional Planning Commission (Box 16, Folder 64)
  - UDAG (Box 16, Folder 65)
  - Underclass (Box 16, Folder 66)
  - Urban Studies (Box 16, Folder 67)
  - Veatch Rehab Proposal (Box 16, Folder 68)
  - Veatch- school segregation (Box 16, Folder 69)
  - Veatch proposals (Box 16, Folder 70)
  - Veronica Whitaker's material (Box 16, Folder 71)
  - Steve Weil (Box 16, Folder 72)
- Series VIII. Correspondence
  - January-May 1970 (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - June-September 1970 (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - October-December 1970 (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - January-June 1971 (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - July-September 1971 (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - October-December 1971 (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - January-April 1972 (Box 17, Folder 7)
  - May-July 1972 (Box 17, Folder 8)
  - August-October 1972 (Box 17, Folder 9)
  - November-December 1972 (Box 17, Folder 10)
  - December 1973 (Box 17, Folder 11)
  - January 1974 (Box 17, Folder 12)
  - February-April 1974 (Box 17, Folder 13)
  - May-June 1974 (Box 17, Folder 14)
  - July-September 1974 (Box 17, Folder 15)
  - October-December 1974 (Box 17, Folder 16)
  - January-April 1976 (Box 17, Folder 17)
  - May 1976 (Box 17, Folder 18)
  - June 1976 (Box 17, Folder 19)
  - January-March 1975 (Box 17, Folder 20)
  - April - June 1975 (Box 17, Folder 21)
  - July-Dec. 1975 (Box 17, Folder 22)
  - Miscellaneous correspondence, 1964-1966 (Box 17, Folder 23)
  - Miscellaneous correspondence, 1965 (Box 17, Folder 24)
  - Miscellaneous correspondence, 1966 (Box 17, Folder 25-26)
  - Miscellaneous correspondence, 1967 (Box 17, Folder 27-28)
  - Miscellaneous correspondence, 1968 (Box 17, Folder 29)
  - Miscellaneous correspondence, 1968-1969 (Box 17, Folder 30)
  - Miscellaneous correspondence, 1969 (Box 17, Folder 31)
  - Miscellaneous correspondence, 1969-1971 (Box 17, Folder 32-34)
  - Miscellaneous correspondence, 1970 (Box 17, Folder 35)
  - Miscellaneous correspondence, 1972 (Box 17, Folder 36-38)
  - September-December 1982 (Box 17, Folder 39)
  - January-November 1983 (Box 17, Folder 40)
  - Miscellaneous correspondence, 1983-1984 (Box 17, Folder 41)
- Series IX. Project files
  - Interjurisdictional Section 8- Akron and Portage MAA's Administration (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - Interjurisdictional Use of Section 8 - NEFCO discussion papers, Sept. 5, 1979 (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - Meetings held at NEFCO on SAI Proposal (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - Professor Julie Saltman (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - Akron NAACP (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - Canton Urban League (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - NEFCO (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - NEFCO- Fair Housing Contact Services (Box 18, Folder 8)
  - Proposal to NEFCO, July 17, 1979 (Box 18, Folder 9)
  - NEFCO - Goal Statement (Box 18, Folder 10)
  - NEFCO - Land Banking Program, August-September 1979 (Box 18, Folder 11)
  - NEFCO - Akron/Canton Intensive Technical Asst. (Box 18, Folder 12)
  - Housing Advocates, Inc. (Box 18, Folder 13)
  - Boston Groups, organizations (Box 18, Folder 14)
  - Boston Proposal (Box 18, Folder 15)
  - Housing Info., Referral and Counseling Program, 1979 (Box 18, Folder 16)
  - Boston - League of Women Voters (Box 18, Folder 17)
  - Boston - Mayor's Office of Fair Housing - Eric McFadden (Box 18, Folder 18)
  - Boston - Citizen's Housing and Planning Association (Box 18, Folder 19)
  - Boston - Testing Program- Section 8, September 1979 (Box 18, Folder 20)
  - Boston - Metropolitan Area Planning Council (Box 18, Folder 21)
  - Boston - Education/Instruccione (Box 18, Folder 22)
  - Boston - Low Income Planning Aid (Box 18, Folder 23)
  - Boston - NAACP (Box 18, Folder 24)
  - South Shore Coalition for Human Rights (Box 18, Folder 25)
  - Boston - Massachusetts Commission Against Discrimination (Box 18, Folder 26)
  - General meeting- MAPC, August 29, 1979 (Box 18, Folder 27)
  - Boston - Intensive Technical Assistance (Box 18, Folder 28)
  - Counseling (Box 18, Folder 29-32)
  - Norfolk - Intensive Tech. Assistance (Box 18, Folder 33)
  - Norfolk - NAACP (Box 18, Folder 34)
  - Norfolk Legal Aid (Box 18, Folder 35)
  - Norfolk - Tidewater Fair Housing- Ellis James (Box 18, Folder 36)
  - Norfolk - Initial Site Visit, February 15-16, 1979 (Box 18, Folder 37)
  - Norfolk - Urban League of Tidewater, Virginia (Box 18, Folder 38)
  - Norfolk Area - coalition- Robert Williams (Box 18, Folder 39)
  - Norfolk - League of Women Voters (Box 18, Folder 40)
  - Norfolk S.V.P.D.C. - Proposal for Technical Assistance (Box 18, Folder 41)
  - Norfolk - Portsmouth NAACP (Box 18, Folder 42)
  - Norfolk - S.T.O.P. Organization (Box 18, Folder 43)
  - Norfolk - S.V.P.D.C. (Box 18, Folder 44)
  - S.V.P.D.C. Regional Housing Mobility Program (Box 18, Folder 45)
  - Shopping Facilities in the Norfolk - Virginia Beach - Portsmouth Area (Box 18, Folder 46)
  - Southeastern Virginia Planning District and Studies (Box 18, Folder 47)
  - Southeastern Virginia Planning Commission (Box 18, Folder 48)
  - Southeastern Virginia Transportation Control Plan (Box 18, Folder 49)
  - The Huntersville II Workshop Findings (Box 18, Folder 50)
  - The Church Street Workshop Findings (Box 18, Folder 51)
  - Texas Current (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - New Town Current Notes (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - Texas Motion Papers (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - CDBG File - Port Arthur (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - Miscellaneous notes (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - Port Arthur Public Assistance Housing (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - Voting Rights Case (Box 19, Folder 7)
  - Mosleley Clippings (Box 19, Folder 8)
  - P.U.C.D. (Box 19, Folder 9)
  - Title VI and VII Complaints (Box 19, Folder 10)
  - Palomar v. HUD (Box 19, Folder 11)
  - Texas (Box 19, Folder 12)
  - Correspondence (Box 19, Folder 13)
  - Notes, April 1983 (Box 19, Folder 14)
  - Port Arthur Census Data (Box 19, Folder 15)
  - New Community Regulations (Box 19, Folder 16)
  - Port Arthur notes (Box 19, Folder 17)
  - Maps (Box 19, Folder 18)
  - Texarkana Case (Box 19, Folder 19)
  - Hunt clippings (Box 19, Folder 20)
  - Cogent clippings (Box 19, Folder 21)
  - Tax Increment Zones (Box 19, Folder 22)
  - Real Estate ads (Box 19, Folder 23)
  - Street paving/drainage (Box 19, Folder 24)
  - New Town Funding Sources (Box 19, Folder 25)
  - Port Arthur Memo #1 (Box 19, Folder 26)
  - Affirmative Action Marketing (Box 19, Folder 27)
  - Port Arthur Maps (Box 19, Folder 28)
  - Relevant regulations (Box 19, Folder 29)
  - Model Economic Development Assessments (Box 19, Folder 30)
  - Zoning (Box 19, Folder 31)
  - Port Arthur Housing Strategy/HAP (Box 19, Folder 32)
  - New Town- newspaper clippings (Box 19, Folder 33)
  - APA Housing Trust Fund Proposals (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - Port Arthur- legal (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - South Eastern Texas Regional Planning Commission Reports (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - New Community Files (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - Port Arthur Master Plan, 1973 (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - U.D.A.G. Paybacks (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - U.D.A.G. Project (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - MAI correspondence (Box 20, Folder 8)
  - New Town Court papers (Box 20, Folder 9)
  - Port Arthur meetings & phone calls (Box 20, Folder 10)
  - Port Arthur photos (Box 20, Folder 11)
  - Church fund raising (Hoboken) (Box 20, Folder 12)
  - Long Island City - development (industry profile) (Box 20, Folder 13)
  - Waterfront development- Port Authority/Long Island City (Box 20, Folder 14)
  - Waterfront testimony (orig.) (Box 20, Folder 15)
  - Hoboken Waterfront Bill (Box 20, Folder 16)
  - Hoboken meetings/correspondence (Box 20, Folder 17)
  - Hoboken Needs Assessment/Proposal (Box 20, Folder 18)
  - Hoboken (Box 20, Folder 19-20)
  - Hoboken Grant Proposal (Box 20, Folder 21)
  - Lower East Side (1st of 5) (Box 20, Folder 22)
  - New York City Special Districts & Precedents (Box 20, Folder 23)
  - Lower East Side Zoning memos & drafts (Box 20, Folder 24)
  - Lower East Side Current (Box 20, Folder 25)
  - Lower East Side Zoning District, final draft (Box 20, Folder 26)
  - Lower East Side Zoning meetings (Box 20, Folder 27)
  - Final Report notes (Box 20, Folder 28)
  - National Model Search (Box 20, Folder 29)
  - City Charter (Box 20, Folder 30)